tourneytime.com 2019-05-28

# TourneyTime Privacy

TourneyTime, LLC has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: [https://www.tourneytime.com](https://www.tourneytime.com/). 

### Data Collection

TourneyTime may use the information collected to improve the content of our service, customize the content and/or layout of our pages for each individual visitor and diagnose problems with the web server. We may collect only the IP address, domain name, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, user-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the user, such as survey information, contests, and/or site registrations and the registration information. 

TourneyTime's registration form requires users to provide contact information (like name, email address, etc.). This captured data will be used to identify the user to TourneyTime.com, personalize the TourneyTime.com experience, send the user information about our company, updates for upcoming events, or notifications when action is required on the user's behalf. Users may opt-in and opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

We use cookies to customize web page content specific to each member in order to enhance your TourneTime experience and provide security while using our website. 

With respect to Ad Servers: We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies at this time. 

TourneyTime's member data and information will not be sold or provided to another entity, except in the event of a merger or acquisition of TourneyTime.com, LLC. 

### Content

**Third Party Links:** This site may contain links to third party sites. **TourneyTime.com, LLC** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any such Web sites. TourneyTime.com, LLC is not liable for any linked content. 

**Public Forums:** This site makes forums, private messging, chat rooms, and/or message boards available to its users in controled areas. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you the user should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. TourneyTime.com, LLC is not liable for any of this information. 

**Security**  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, mis-use, and alteration of the information under our control. TourneyTime, LLC uses a secure and protected database and various application security layers. Additionally, TourneyTime.com uses a secure site certificate to encrypt financial transaction information and no credit card information is stored on TourneyTime servers.. 

### Opt-In/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-in and opt-out of receiving communications from us and/or our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to prevent future communications or to no longer receive our service. The users may select what information they would like to receive and what information they no longer wish to receive.

**Opt-in/Opt-Out of email communications**
  * Opt-out: Users can visit the following URL: [https://www.tourneytime.com/privacy/optout.cfm](https://www.tourneytime.com/privacy/OptOut.cfm)
  * Opt-in/Opt-out: Login to member account and update the member profile and related email communication options
  * Cancel Account: Send email to [support@tourneytime.com](mailto:support@tourneytime.com) or contact [TourneyTime Support](https://www.tourneytime.com/support) to request your account and all related information be permenately removed from the database. For security, users will be asked several confirmation questions before deletion occurrs.

### General

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and we will use for these new purposes only data collected from the time of the policy change forward. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site and specifically this privacy policy periodically. 

### Contacting TourneyTime.com, LLC

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices or dealings with this web site, please contact:  
[TourneyTime Support](https://www.tourneytime.com/support). 

TourneyTime.com, LLC  
Eldridge, IA 52748  
Last update: January 7, 2017
